Guide to the Small Towns Institute Records 1956-2002 (bulk 1969-1997)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Small Towns Institute Records
1956-2002 (bulk 1969-1997)
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG042a-05-82
Small Towns Institute (U.S.)
60.0 cubic feet 110 letter sized document cases; 11 letter half sized document cases and 2 legal half sized document cases Correspondence, newspaper clippings, records, subject files, photographs, slides and photographic negatives in good condition
The collection consists of correspondence, subject files, newspaper clippings, photographs, publications and financial and organizational records kept by the Small Towns Institute of Ellensburg, WA, from 1969 to 2002.
Historical Note
The Small Towns Institute was incorporated by the State of Washington on January 8, 1969, as a non-profit organization to research and disseminate information on the plights and problems associated with small town communities primarily in the United States and Canada in the latter part of the 20th century. The concept for a research institute was first proposed by Clayton E. Denman, a professor of anthropology at Central Washington University, on November 1, 1966, as an academic program to be added to the college’s curriculum. On February 13, 1967, Dr. Denman called for the selection of a committee of interested faculty members and administrators to organize the program. After a series of committee meetings on organizational structure and program development, a constitution and by-laws were devised and ratified by the committee on January 4, 1969, and an application for incorporation sent to the Secretary of State of Washington. The Institute was housed on the Central Washington University campus, where it remained until 2001.
The Institute began publishing a short newsletter titled Small Town in July 1969. By the mid 1970s the newsletter had expanded into a monthly magazine and in 1980 it became a bimonthly journal. The Institute also published resource guides, booklets and various pamphlets and brochures related to the preservation of small town communities. From the late 1970s to the mid-1980s, the Small Towns Institute received international recognition and was involved in formulating national policy on rural development, particularly during the administration of President Jimmy Carter. A significant transition occurred during the spring of 1983, when founder and Executive Director Clayton Denman resigned as director after fourteen years. His wife Anne, the Editorial Director for over a decade, submitted her resignation later the same year. Financial woes that had plagued the Institute since the organization’s early years were made considerably worse during the recession of the late 1980s. Sizable private loans, declining memberships and waning journal subscriptions led to financial instabilities in the 1990s. In 2001 the Institute ceased publication of its journal and the following year its offices closed on the Central Washington University campus.
The Ellensburg-based Small Towns Institute records contain clippings from local and regional newspapers, articles from national magazines and journals, government and organizational pamphlets, newsletters, brochures and miscellaneous other publications related to the preservation of small town communities or organizations that support conservation and preservation projects. Also present in the collection are correspondence, photographs and drafts of articles submitted for publication and published in the Institute’s journal Small Town. Included in the correspondence files are letters from members of the United States Congress and other notable state and national politicians.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Organized into seven series: I. Correspondence. II. Subject files. III. Organization files. IV. Article submissions and drafts. V. Photographs for articles. VI. Publications. VII. Financial and miscellaneous records. Arranged alphabetically by subject heading or surname.
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Small Towns Institute (U.S.)
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Rural development--United States; Rural development--Canada; Rural communities
Washington (State); City and Town Life
- Correspondence, 1956-2002; I
  This series consists of in-coming and out-going correspondence from 1956 to 2002. The series was organized by members of the Small Towns Institute and retained in its original order.
  - Correspondence – General, 1970 (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Correspondence – General, 1971 (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence – General, 1971 (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Correspondence – General, 1972 (Box-folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence – General, 1973 (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Correspondence – General, 1973 (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Correspondence – General, 1974 (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Correspondence – General, 1975 (Box-folder 1-8)
  - Correspondence – General, 1976 (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Correspondence – General, 1976 (Box-folder 1-10)
  - Correspondence – General, 1977 (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Correspondence – General, 1978 (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Correspondence – General, 1979 (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Correspondence – General, 1980 (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence – General, 1981 (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Correspondence – General, 1982 (Box-folder 2-5)
  - Correspondence – General, 1983 (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Correspondence – General, 1984 (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Correspondence – General, 1984 (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Correspondence – General, 1984 (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Correspondence – General, 1984 (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Correspondence – General, 1985 (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Correspondence – General, 1985 (Box-folder 2-12)
  - Correspondence – General, 1985 (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Correspondence – General, 1985 (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Correspondence – General, 1986 (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Correspondence – General, 1986 (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence – General, 1986 (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Correspondence – General, 1986 (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Correspondence – General, 1987 (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Correspondence – General, 1987 (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Correspondence – General, 1988 (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Correspondence – General, 1988 (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Correspondence – General, 1989 (Box-folder 4-3)
  - Correspondence – General, 1989 (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Correspondence – General, 1990 (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Correspondence – General, 1990 (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Correspondence – General, 1990 (Box-folder 4-7)
  - Correspondence – General, 1991 (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Correspondence – General, 1991 (Box-folder 4-9)
  - Correspondence – General, 1992 (Box-folder 4-10)
  - Correspondence – General, 1993 (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Correspondence – General, 1994 (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Correspondence – General, 1995 (Box-folder 5-3)
  - Correspondence – General, 1996 (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Correspondence – General, 1997 (Box-folder 5-5)
  - Correspondence – General, 1998 (Box-folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence – General, 1999 (Box-folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence – General, 2000 (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Correspondence – General, 2001 (Box-folder 5-9)
  - Correspondence – Advisory Board, 1969-1982 (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Correspondence – Burlington Northern, 1982 (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Correspondence – Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1978 (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Correspondence – Employment, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Correspondence – Employment, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 6-5)
  - Correspondence – Foundation Grants, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Correspondence – Government Agencies, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence – Jakubauskas, Edward, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 6-8)
  - Correspondence – Kendall, Henry P., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 6-9)
  - Correspondence – Kennedy, J. F., 1970 (Box-folder 6-10)
  - Correspondence – Klemme, Randall, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 6-11)
  - Correspondence – MacDonald, Greg, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 6-12)
  - Correspondence – Members of Congress, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 6-13)
  - Correspondence – Mount Holyoke Alumnae Quarterly Article Response, 1974 (Box-folder 6-14)
  - Correspondence – Munsell, Kenneth, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 6-15)
  - Correspondence – Munsell, Kenneth, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 6-16)
  - Correspondence – Munsell, Kenneth, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 6-17)
  - Correspondence – National Endowment for the Arts, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 7-1)
  - Correspondence – National Endowment for the Arts, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Correspondence – National Endowment for the Arts, Grant, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Correspondence – National Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Correspondence – National Trust for Historic Preservation, Grants and Special Issue, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Correspondence – Office of Small Town Services, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Correspondence – Proposed issue, Pets, 1982 (Box-folder 7-7)
  - Correspondence – Proposed issue, Manufactured Housing, 1982 (Box-folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence – Quinn, Bernard, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 7-9)
  - Correspondence – Regarding exchanges, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Correspondence – Regarding exchanges, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 7-11)
  - Correspondence – Regarding exchanges, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 7-12)
  - Correspondence – Regarding support for Weyehaeuser Design, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 7-13)
  - Correspondence – Reprint permission requests, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Correspondence – Reprint permission requests, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Correspondence – Resource Council Formation, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 7-16)
  - Correspondence – Robertson, James, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 7-17)
  - Correspondence – Tarton, John, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 7-18)
- Subject files, 1969-1998; II
  This series consists of alphabetically arranged subject files from 1969 to 1998. The series was organized by members of the Small Towns Institute and retained in its original order.
  - Agriculture – Corporate, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Agriculture – Exports and imports, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Agriculture – Farm bills, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Agriculture – Farm economy, 1969-1983 (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Agriculture – Farm economy, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Agriculture – Farm economy, 1986 (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Agriculture – Farm economy, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 8-7)
  - Agriculture – Farm economy, 1989-1998 (Box-folder 9-1)
  - Agriculture – New York State Department of Agriculture Bulletin (Box-folder 9-2)
  - Agriculture – Prices, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 9-3)
  - Agriculture – Technology, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 9-4)
  - Agriculture – Women, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 9-5)
  - Airlines, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 9-6)
  - Alternate technology, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 9-7)
  - Animal control, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 9-8)
  - Appropriate technology, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 9-9)
  - Archeology, 1973-1989 (Box-folder 9-10)
  - Architecture, 1973-1991 (Box-folder 9-11)
  - Arson, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 9-12)
  - Arts, 1976-1993 (Box-folder 10-1)
  - Arts, 1976-1993 (Box-folder 10-2)
  - Arts, 1976-1993 (Box-folder 10-3)
  - Arts – Community Theater, Colorado City, Texas, 1986 (Box-folder 10-4)
  - Arts – Community Development, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 10-5)
  - Arts – Community Development, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 10-6)
  - Arts – Crafts and craft people, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 10-7)
  - Arts – Facilities, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 10-8)
  - Arts – Ink people, 1985 (Box-folder 10-9)
  - Arts – Performing, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 11-1)
  - Arts – Performing, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 11-2)
  - Arts – Public murals, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 11-3)
  - Arts – State Arts Council, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 11-4)
  - Arts – State Arts Council, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 11-5)
  - Arts – State Arts Council, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 12-1)
  - Arts – State Arts Council, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 12-2)
  - Arts – Tourism, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 13-1)
  - Arts – Visual, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 13-2)
  - Arts – Wasua, Washington, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13-3)
  - Banking – Federal Reserves, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13-4)
  - Banking – Federal Reserves, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 13-5)
  - Banks, 1972-1996 (Box-folder 13-6)
  - Banks, 1972-1996 (Box-folder 13-7)
  - Banks, 1972-1996 (Box-folder 13-8)
  - Bandshells, 1981 (Box-folder 14-1)
  - Beautification, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 14-2)
  - Bicentennial, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 14-3)
  - Bicentennial, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 14-4)
  - Bicycling, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 14-5)
  - Bicycling, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 14-6)
  - Bicycling – Ohio Bikeway Communicator (Newsletter), 1974-1986 (Box-folder 14-7)
  - Boomtowns, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 14-8)
  - Boomtowns, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 14-9)
  - Bridges, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 15-1)
  - Bureaucracy, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 15-2)
  - Business values, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 15-3)
  - Business values, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 15-4)
  - Bus transportation, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 15-5)
  - Cable Television, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 15-6)
  - Cable Television, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 15-7)
  - Church and Community, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 15-8)
  - Church and Community, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 15-9)
  - Citizenship and Leadership, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 16-1)
  - Civil Defense, 1979 (Box-folder 16-2)
  - Cities, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 16-3)
  - Cities – Government, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 16-4)
  - Clear City Committees, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 16-5)
  - Coal Gasification, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 16-6)
  - Company towns, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 16-7)
  - Communications, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 16-8)
  - Communes, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 16-9)
  - Communes – 19th Century Zoar, Ohio, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 16-10)
  - Community, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 17-1)
  - Community, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 17-2)
  - Community - Centers, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 17-3)
  - Community Center – Castle Rock Hall (Box-folder 17-4)
  - Community development, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 17-5)
  - Community development, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 18-1)
  - Community development, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 18-2)
  - Community development, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 18-3)
  - Community development – Block grants, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 18-4)
  - Community development – Block grants, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 18-5)
  - Community development – Block grants, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 18-6)
  - Community development – David, Kentucky, 1980 (Box-folder 18-7)
  - Community development – Governor’s Awards (Box-folder 18-8)
  - Community foundations, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 19-1)
  - Community foundations, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 19-2)
  - Community land trusts, 1992 (Box-folder 19-3)
  - Community of Ellensburg Information, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 19-4)
  - Community of Grinnel Foundation, 1986 (Box-folder 19-5)
  - Community of Wabash Foundation, 1986 (Box-folder 19-6)
  - Community Profile – Kutztown (Box-folder 19-7)
  - Community survey of Ellensburg, 1990 (Box-folder 19-8)
  - Computer, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 19-9)
  - Conservation, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 19-10)
  - Conservation – Commissions (Box-folder 19-11)
  - Consumer, 1979 (Box-folder 19-12)
  - Consumer, 1980 (Box-folder 19-13)
  - Cooperatives, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 19-14)
  - Corporate responsibility, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20-1)
  - County government, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 20-2)
  - Crime, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 20-3)
  - Crime, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 20-4)
  - Crime, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 20-5)
  - Crime – Prevention, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 20-6)
  - Crime – Prevention, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 20-7)
  - Cultural Center – Thomasville, Georgia, 1988 (Box-folder 20-8)
  - Day Care, 1989 (Box-folder 20-9)
  - Decentralization, 1983 (Box-folder 20-10)
  - Demographics, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 20-11)
  - Demographics, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 20-12)
  - Demographics, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 20-13)
  - Design, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 21-1)
  - Design, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 21-2)
  - Design, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 21-3)
  - Design – Columbus, Indiana, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 21-4)
  - Design – Competitions, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 21-5)
  - Design – Guidelines – Brunswick, Maine, 1991 (Box-folder 21-6)
  - Design – Guidelines – Park City, Utah, 1985 (Box-folder 21-7)
  - Design – Guidelines – Park City, Utah (Box-folder 21-8)
  - Design – North Carolina Henry Saraff Project, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 21-9)
  - Design Review, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 21-10)
  - Design – Spring Green, Wisconsin, 1980 (Box-folder 21-11)
  - Design – Workshops, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 21-12)
  - Development, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 22-1)
  - Development, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 22-2)
  - Disaster planning, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 22-3)
  - Disaster planning, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 22-4)
  - Disaster planning, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 22-5)
  - Disaster planning – Earthquakes, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 22-6)
  - Disaster planning – Earthquakes, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 22-7)
  - Downtown – Baker City, Oregon, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 23-1)
  - Downtown – Beloit, Wisconsin, 1978 (Box-folder 23-2)
  - Downtown – Canada, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 23-3)
  - Downtown – Canada, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 23-4)
  - Downtown – Corapolis, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box-folder 23-5)
  - Downtown – Facade Guidelines, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 23-6)
  - Downtown – Healdsburg, California, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 23-7)
  - Downtown – Lancaster, Texas, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 23-8)
  - Downtown – Loveland, Colorado, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 23-9)
  - Downtown – Medina, Ohio, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 23-10)
  - Downtown – Meridian, Mississippi, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 23-11)
  - Downtown – New buildings, grade two, 1994 (Box-folder 23-12)
  - Downtown – Promotions, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 24-1)
  - Downtown – Portland, Connecticut, 1980 (Box-folder 24-2)
  - Downtown – Red Springs, North Carolina, 1980 (Box-folder 24-3)
  - Downtown – Revitalization theory, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 24-4)
  - Downtown – Winchester, Massachusetts, 1979 (Box-folder 24-5)
  - Downtown – Utica, New York, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 24-6)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Bloomfield, Nebraska, 1997 (Box-folder 25-1)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Brooke Station, Virginia, 1993 (Box-folder 25-2)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Cle Elum and Roslyn, 1989 (Box-folder 25-3)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Connecticut River, 1995 (Box-folder 25-4)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Cortes, British Columbia, 1995 (Box-folder 25-5)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Esparto, California, 1993 (Box-folder 25-6)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Fayettville, Arkansas, 1994 (Box-folder 25-6a)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Haines Junction, Alaska, 1994 (Box-folder 25-7)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Kittitas County, Washington, 1991 (Box-folder 25-8)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Oyster Bay / Buttle Lake, British Columbia, 1996 (Box-folder 25-9)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Port Colborne, Ontario (Box-folder 25-10)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Quadra Island, 1996 (Box-folder 25-11)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Rogers, Arkansas, 1990 (Box-folder 25-12)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Rural Comox Valley, British Columbia, 1998 (Box-folder 25-13)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Saint Claire, Michigan, 1994 (Box-folder 25-14)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – San Diego, California (Box-folder 25-15)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – San Diego, California (Box-folder 25-16)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Scarsdale, Arizona, 1994 (Box-folder 25-17)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Soledad, California, 1994 (Box-folder 26-1)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Whistler, British Columbia, 1991 (Box-folder 26-2)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Whistler, British Columbia, 1991 (Box-folder 26-3)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Yakima, Washington, 1997 (Box-folder 26-4)
  - Downtown Comprehensive Plan – Yellow Springs, Ohio, 1996 (Box-folder 26-5)
  - Economy, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 27-1)
  - Economy, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 27-2)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-3)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-4)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-5)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-6)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-7)
  - Economic Development, 1976-1985 (Box-folder 27-8)
  - Economic Development – Bow Island, Alberta, 1989 (Box-folder 28-1)
  - Economic Development – Business Incubators, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 28-2)
  - Economic Development – Business Incubators, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 28-3)
  - Economic Development – Colorado Initiatives, 1988 (Box-folder 28-4)
  - Economic Development – Community Development Corporations, 1988 (Box-folder 28-5)
  - Economic Development – Community Profiles, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 28-6)
  - Economic Development – Community Profiles, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 28-7)
  - Economic Development – Community Profiles, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 28-8)
  - Economic Development – Community Case Studies, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 28-9)
  - Economic Development – Community Case Studies, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 28-10)
  - Economic Development – Costs and Benefits, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 29-1)
  - Economic Development – Costs and Benefits, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 29-2)
  - Economic Development – Federal Laws, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 29-3)
  - Economic Development – Native Americans, 1980 (Box-folder 29-4)
  - Economic Development – New Berne, North Carolina, 1985 (Box-folder 29-5)
  - Economic Development – Plant Sites, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 29-6)
  - Economic Development – State Programs, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 29-7)
  - Economic Development – State Programs, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 29-8)
  - Economic Development – State Programs, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 30-1)
  - Economic Development – State Programs, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 30-2)
  - Education, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 30-3)
  - Education, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 30-4)
  - Education, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 30-5)
  - Education, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 30-6)
  - Ellensburg, Washington, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 31-1)
  - Employment, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 31-2)
  - Employment, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 31-3)
  - Employment, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 31-4)
  - Energy, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 32-1)
  - Energy, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 32-2)
  - Energy, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 32-3)
  - Energy, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 32-4)
  - Energy, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 32-5)
  - Energy - Electricity, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 32-6)
  - Energy – Gas, 1977 (Box-folder 33-1)
  - Energy – Hydroelectric, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 33-2)
  - Energy – Hydroelectric, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 33-3)
  - Energy – Lightning, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 33-4)
  - Energy – Nuclear, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 33-5)
  - Energy – Nuclear, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 33-6)
  - Energy – Nuclear, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 33-7)
  - Energy – Oil, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 34-1)
  - Energy – “People and Energy" Periodical, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 34-2)
  - Energy – Solar, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 34-3)
  - Energy – Solar, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 34-4)
  - Energy – Solar, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 34-5)
  - Energy – Wind, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 34-6)
  - Energy – Wood Burning and Stoves, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 34-7)
  - Enterprise Zones, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 34-8)
  - Environment, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 35-1)
  - Environment, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 35-2)
  - Environment, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 35-3)
  - Environment, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 35-4)
  - Factory Closures, 1971-1982 (Box-folder 35-5)
  - Family, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 35-6)
  - Family Farm, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 36-1)
  - Family Farm, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 36-2)
  - Farm and Community, 1988 (Box-folder 36-3)